[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "questionText": "question_what_private_parts",
    "answer": "answer_private_parts",
    "topicId": 1,
    "minAge": 8,
    "maxAge": 12,
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "questionText": "question_why_keep_clean",
    "answer": "answer_keep_clean",
    "topicId": 1,
    "minAge": 8,
    "maxAge": 15,
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "questionText": "question_what_private_parts_2",
    "answer": "answer_private_parts_2",
    "topicId": 1,
    "minAge": 10,
    "maxAge": 15,
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "questionText": "question_how_stay_safe",
    "answer": "answer_stay_safe",
    "topicId": 2,
    "minAge": 8,
    "maxAge": 15,
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "questionText": "question_good_bad_touch",
    "answer": "answer_good_bad_touch",
    "topicId": 2,
    "minAge": 8,
    "maxAge": 12,
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "questionText": "question_who_trust",
    "answer": "answer_who_trust",
    "topicId": 2,
    "minAge": 10,
    "maxAge": 15,
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "questionText": "question_what_puberty",
    "answer": "answer_puberty",
    "topicId": 3,
    "minAge": 10,
    "maxAge": 15,
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "questionText": "question_confused_changes",
    "answer": "answer_confused_changes",
    "topicId": 3,
    "minAge": 10,
    "maxAge": 15,
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "questionText": "question_when_talk_changes",
    "answer": "answer_when_talk_changes",
    "topicId": 3,
    "minAge": 10,
    "maxAge": 15,
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "questionText": "question_how_make_friends",
    "answer": "answer_make_friends",
    "topicId": 4,
    "minAge": 8,
    "maxAge": 15,
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "questionText": "question_someone_mean",
    "answer": "answer_someone_mean",
    "topicId": 4,
    "minAge": 8,
    "maxAge": 12,
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "questionText": "question_bullying_help",
    "answer": "answer_bullying_help",
    "topicId": 4,
    "minAge": 8,
    "maxAge": 15,
    "difficulty": "medium"
  }
]
